Honey
These frogs sold well
3 million in net profit
As we agreed
we should get 200,000 or 300,000
We can finally hold our heads high
I'm hanging up
Daniel is back from settling the accounts
Brother-in-law, I'm rich
These frogs made 3 million in net profit
Come here
This is your money
50,000
I borrowed 50,000 from you two years ago
Now I'm paying you back
Totally fair
Borrowed
You said you were short on cash
and asked me for 50,000 to be partners
You must have misheard
50,000 to buy into the business
Dream on
Brother-in-law
I want to use my family's
forestland to raise forest frogs
But I'm broke
Give me 50,000
It'll count as your investment
I'll split the profit with you half-half
Drink some water
Cynthia
Withdraw the 40,000 from our savings
The remaining 10,000
I'll go borrow
Daniel
Just go for it
I'll cover any losses
If we make money, you decide the split
Lewes, don't you worry
We'll split it fifty‑fifty
This past year
I lived and ate at the farm
tending to the forest frogs
and figuring out the extraction process
I finally bred
high-quality forest frogs
and produced premium forest frog oil
Buyers were fighting
to pay top price for it
Fine
Let's say I misheard
But what about my wages for two years
You just fed the frogs
Anyone could do that
How dare you ask for money
Only because you're my brother-in-law
I gave you room and board
and let you learn the trade
I haven't even charged you yet
Daniel
Have some conscience
I've been at your farm
for two full years
breeding and feeding
-Enough
-tending, processing
I'm sick of your nagging
Listen
I'll pay you 1,000 a month
to assist a college grad I just hired
1,000
Not happy
For my sister's sake
I'm giving you this money
I quit
Good riddance
Saves me the money
Don't come crawling back later
Boss
How much to rent the greenhouse
30,000 a year
Non-negotiable
I'll take it
Let's sign the contract now